Guide to the National Coalition for Haitian Rights Records, 1964-2020, bulk 1982-2004 RL.11314
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1964-2008, undated; bulk 1980-2006; 5; 89 boxes
  - Anti-Slavery International to McCalla, 1991 (Box 70)
  - Antoine Izmery assassination [h], 1993 (Box 70)
  - Antoine Izmery murder, 1993 (Box 70)
  - ANUR, 1993 (Box 70)
  - APAB to Inter-American Foundation, 1992 (Box 70)
  - APENA - Clifford Larose, 1998 (Box 146)
  - APN arrests, 1989 (Box 70)
  - Appel pour les quatriemes Assises europeennes sur la droit d'asile, 1993 (Box 70)
  - AQOCI, Human Rights Violations in Haiti, 1993 (Box 70)
  - Archbishop Bevilacqua letter, 1991 (Box 70)
  - Archbishop of Philadelphia to President Bush, 1992 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - press conference, 1990 (Box 150)
  - Aristide - "Aristide's militia denied by Geneva Police", 1991 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - "Jean Bertrand Aristide: Portrait", 1990 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - "Reflections of President Aristide on political situation in Haiti", 1991 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - Accord Protocol between President Aristide and Prime Minister Rene Theodore, 1992 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - Agreement for the return of President Aristide, 1992 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - American Supporters, 1992 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - Americans for Aristide correspondence with editor NY Times, 1991 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - Americans for Aristide urgent appeal, 1991 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - Anti-Aristide material, 1991 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - Aristide address to the National Press Club, 1994 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - Aristide Foundation for Democracy, 1996 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - Aristide Meetings, etc., 1992 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - Aristide NY visit, 1990 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - Aristide speech at Senate, 1991 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - Aristide statements, 1991 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - Aristide's itinerary, 1991 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - Aristide's message to Haiti, 1991 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - Aristide's speech, 1991 (Box 70)
  - Aristide - Aristide's speech, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - Aristide's speech at UN, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - Committee to protect journalists to Aristide, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - Concentration on Haiti Correspondence/letter to Aristide, 1995 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - Correspondence/letter to Aristide from Chamber of Deputees, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - Correspondence/letter to Aristide from Marie-Yola Dennis, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - Correspondence/letter to Aristide from McCalla, 1993 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - Correspondence/letter to President Aristide, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - decree of Amnesty by Aristide, 1993 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - Haiti: crisis, intervention, Aristide and the working classes, 1994 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - Human Rights in haiti under Aristide, 1993 (Box 150)
  - Aristide - Human Rights in Haiti under Aristide, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - International Liaison Office- President Aristide, 1994 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - Lavalas/Aristide politics, 2000 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - Les Sept Mois de la Presidence du Pere Jean-Bertrand Aristide (The Seven Months of Father Jean-Bertrand Aristide's Presidency) given by a.i. Prime Minister Jn. Jacques Honorat, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - Notes comparing death toll under Aristide vs. Trouillot vs. Avril, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - notes on the establishment of a protocol for the return of Aristide, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - Operation Persuasion Plan to get Haitian Parliament to convict Jean Bertrand Aristide and Rene Preval for High Treason, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - President Aristide- Haiti update, 1995 (Box 150)
  - Aristide - protocol between Aristide and Parliament, 1992 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - Report: One year under Aristide, 1995 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - resolution in support of the constitutional government of Aristide, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Aristide - UN Aristide's Speech, 1993 (Box 71)
  - Aristide- Haiti Update, 1995 (Box 71)
  - Armed Forces of Haiti Press Release, 1993 (Box 71)
  - Army abuses, 1990 (Box 71)
  - Army arrests, 1990 (Box 150)
  - Army issues, 1990 (Box 71)
  - Aronson, suspend deportation, 1990 (Box 71)
  - Arrest of Altide Luisdor Mathieu, 1992 (Box 71)
  - Arrest of Guerre, 1989 (Box 71)
  - Arrest of journalists, 1992 (Box 71)
  - Arrested list, 1991 (Box 116)
  - Arrested students list, 1991 (Box 116)
  - Arrests, 1986-1989 (Box 71)
  - Article written by NCHR staff published in The Guardian: New Hopes as Civilians Take the Reins in Haiti, 1990 (Box 71)
  - Assassination of Haitian Justice Minister Guy Malary, 1994 (Box 72)
  - Assembly of Concentration on the Political Human Rights situation in Haiti, 1990 (Box 117)
  - Assessing Prison Conditions, 1992 (Box 72)
  - Assessment of the Haitian In-Country Refugee Program, 1993 (Box 72)
  - Assessment of US protection of human rights activists in Haiti, 1993 (Box 72)
  - Assistance for Haiti (draft), 1989 (Box 72)
  - Assistance to a democratic Haiti draft proposal, 1991 (Box 72)
  - Assistance to Democratic Haiti- Proposal Draft for a Conference, 1991 (Box 72)
  - Associate Counsel of UNHCR meeting, 1994 (Box 117)
  - Association for Haitian American Development to McCalla, 1998 (Box 72)
  - Association for Haitian American Development Correspondence/letters, 1998 (Box 72)
  - Association of Haitian Entrepreneurs Business and Health Fair, 1995 (Box 72)
  - Association of Haitian Immigrant Women, 1995 (Box 72)
  - Association of Haitian Journalists, 1988 (Box 72)
  - Association of Haitian Journalists, 1989 (Box 72)
  - Association of Haitian Physicians mail, 1997-1998 (Box 72)
  - Association of the Bar of the City of New York in Brief, 1992 (Box 72)
  - Asylum and Safe Haven Bulletin, 1992 (Box 72)
  - Asylum and Safe Haven Issues Bulletin, 1992 (Box 72)
  - Asylum and Safe Haven Task Force Conference Call, 1992 (Box 72)
  - Asylum applications, 1993 (Box 72)
  - Asylum applications received, 1992 (Box 116)
  - Asylum materials (includes reports and declarations), 1992-1993 (Box 72)
  - Asylum Prescreening, 1991 (Box 72)
  - Atlanta Haitian Community Center, 2001 (Box 72)
  - Atlanta Journal article, 1991 (Box 72)
  - Attack on Pierre Esperance (NCHR Executive Director), 1999 (Box 72)
  - Attempted coup, 1989 (Box 72)
  - Avril - Alleged IHRED document: proposal for General Avril's political strategy, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Avril - Anti-Avril petition, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Avril - CPJ letter to Avril, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Avril - Decree from the military government to Avril, 1989 (Box 73)
  - Avril - Key events leading to General Avril's overthrow, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Avril - letter about Avril, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Avril - letter from PANPRA to Avril, 1989 (Box 73)
  - Avril - letter from PNDPH to Avril, 1988 (Box 73)
  - Avril - letter from the Committee to Avril, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Avril - letter to Avril from French Evangelical Church of NY, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Avril - letter to Avril from NCHR, 1989 (Box 73)
  - Avril - letter to Avril with report, 1989 (Box 73)
  - Avril - Lt. Gen. Prosper Avril, 1989 (Box 73)
  - Avril - NCHR Americas Watch letter to Avril, 1989 (Box 73)
  - Avril - NCHR letter to Avril, 1989 (Box 73)
  - Avril - Notes on events and persons under General Avril presidency, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Avril - Notes on political unrest under General Avril, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Avril - Press release- Avril's case, 1991 (Box 73)
  - Avril - Protest letter to Avril, 1989 (Box 73)
  - Avril - RDC to Avril, 1989 (Box 73)
  - Avril - Ruling- Evans Paul v. Prosper Avril, 1994 (Box 73)
  - Avril - Saint Pierre to Avril, 1989 (Box 152)
  - Avril - speech, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Avril - speech to Presidential Guard, 1990 (Box 73)
  - AW to Ian Martin, 1993 (Box 73)
  - AW, NCHR, CR correspondence, 1989 (Box 73)
  - AW/NCHR to Haitian leaders, 1992 (Box 73)
  - AW/NCHR to Lt. Cedras, 1993 (Box 73)
  - AW/NCHR to Secretary Christopher, 1993 (Box 73)
  - Ayiti Ap Lite, 1995 (Box 73)
  - Ayiti Dwa Moun- mandate, 1993 (Box 73)
  - Backgrounder No. 10, 1989 (Box 152)
  - Bahamas, 1992 (Box 73)
  - Bahamas - "Report on a Human Rights Mission on Haitians in the Bahamas", 1992 (Box 73)
  - Bahamas - Ahpaly Coradin Bahamas report, 1995 (Box 73)
  - Bahamas - Grand Bahamas Human Rights- permission for Calla to visit prisons, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Bahamas - Haitians in Bahamas, 1985-1992 (Box 73)
  - Bahamas - Haitians in Bahamas, 1985 (Box 73)
  - Bahamas - Haitians in the Bahamas, 1992 (Box 73)
  - Bahamas - Haiti-Bahamas Repatriation Accord, 1995 (Box 73)
  - Bahamas - Human Rights violations against Haitian refugees in the Bahamas, 1996 (Box 73)
  - Bahamas - Illegal Immigrants in the Bahamas, 1995 (Box 73)
  - Bahamas - J.J. Honorat to Hooper (Bahamas), 1986 (Box 74)
  - Bahamas - Joe Etienne to Bahamas Rotary Club, 1991 (Box 74)
  - Bahamas - Patrick Gavigan- report on the Bahamas, 1996 (Box 74)
  - Bahamas - Repatriation of Haitians from the Bahamas, 1995 (Box 74)
  - Bahamas - Repatriation of Haitians in the Bahamas, 1994-1995 (Box 74)
  - Bahamas - Treaty Between the Commonwealth of the Bahamas and the Republic of Haiti Regarding Illegal Immigration, 1985 (Box 74)
  - Bahamas - USCC, 1983; 1 of 2 (Box 74)
  - Bahamas - USCC, 1983; 2 of 2 (Box 74)
  - Bajeux appeal, 1989 (Box 74)
  - Bajeux to OR, 1989 (Box 74)
  - Bajeux to Soares, 1991 (Box 117)
  - Baker address to General Assembly, 1989 (Box 74)
  - Bapo Sou Konfliant Konsey Deta e Presidan Trouillot, 1987 (Box 74)
  - Barbara Frey, 1992 (Box 74)
  - Bastien, Patrick, 1994-1995 (Box 74)
  - Bâtonnier Lissade articles, 1991 (Box 74)
  - Bay Area Haitian American Council, 1994 (Box 74)
  - Bayard Rustin, 2004 (Box 74)
  - Beloved-Radio Drive and Telephone Promotion, 1998 (Box 74)
  - Berger briefing on the record on Haiti, 1995 (Box 74)
  - Bernard Aronson statement on Haiti political situation, 1991 (Box 74)
  - Bernard Diederich conversation, 1989 (Box 74)
  - Bertin, Mireine Durocher, press, 1995 (Box 74)
  - Betty Williams to McCalla, 1995 (Box 74)
  - Bilingual Education, 1996-1998 (Box 75)
  - Bill Clinton correspondence, 1992 (Box 75)
  - Biography of Lillian Pierre-Paul, 1992 (Box 75)
  - BIP: "A National Plan is urgent and indispensable", 1988 (Box 75)
  - Bishop Romelus Message, 1990 (Box 75)
  - Bishops' statement, 1989 (Box 75)
  - Black Caucus/Haitian Task Force Conference, 1982 (Box 75)
  - Blaise notes (not copied), 1989-1990, and undated (Box 75)
    [French][Kreyol]
  - Blaise reports, 1990; 1 of 2 (Box 75)
  - Blaise reports, 1990; 2 of 2 (Box 75)
  - Bloc Democratique: Address to the Nation, 1989 (Box 75)
  - Bloodletting, score-setting report (Box 75)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - interviews, 1989 (Box 75)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - "236 More Haitian Boat People Returned by Coast Guard to Haiti", 1989 (Box 75)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - "Freedom of Information Request- Haitian Interdiction", 1990 (Box 75)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - "Inter-Religious Memorial Service for Haitian Boat People", 1992 (Box 75)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - "Migrants- Interdiction Agreement Between US and Haiti", 1981 (Box 75)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - "Policy of Haitian Interdiction, Deportation Morally Wrong", 1991 (Box 75)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - "Time to End Haitian Interdiction", 1989 (Box 75)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - AFF Correspondence/letter to Haitian groups on interdiction, 1989 (Box 75)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Amnesty International Boat Project, 1992 (Box 75)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Annual notes and stats for Haitian boat people, 1987-1989 (Box 75)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Anti-Interdiction Statements - churches, 1990 (Box 75)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Appeals for protection of Haitian Boat People, 1991 (Box 75)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Asylum Pre-Screen Interviews from Haitian boat "My Friend", 1991; 1 of 2 (Box 75)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Asylum Pre-Screen Interviews from Haitian boat "My Friend", 1991; 2 of 2 (Box 75)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Boat People Analysis, 1990 (Box 76)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Campaign to end the "Interdiction" of Haitian Refugees, 1989 (Box 76)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Center for Human Rights and Constitutional Law, 1993 (Box 76)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Center for Human Rights and Constitutional Law- Haitian Interdiction Case, 1994 (Box 76)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - CG Interdiction Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 76)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Challenges to US Interdiction of Haitians, 1989 (Box 76)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - CHRCL documents for Haitian Interdiction FOIA, 1991 (Box 76)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - CHRCL letters requesting info on Haitian Interdiction, 1990 (Box 76)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - CHRCL response to Interdiction petition, 1991 (Box 76)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Chris Henry Article "Boat People Still Trying", 1988 (Box 76)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Coast Guard Haitian Rescue stats, 1981-1993 (Box 76)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Coast Guard Standard rate instruction, 1994 (Box 76)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Coast Guard stats, 1988 (Box 76)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Congress letters campaign against interdiction, 1990 (Box 76)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Correspondence on Haitian Interdiction Cases, 1994 (Box 76)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Correspondence/letter to Towners, 1984 (Box 76)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - documents on Haitian interdiction, 1993 (Box 76)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Draft Plan for Campaign against Interdiction, 1989 (Box 77)
  - Boat People/Interdiction - Faxes to politicians, 1991 (Box 152)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Gina's Interdiction Stuff, 1981-1990 (Box 77)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Haiti: Crisis, Interdiction and Detention, 1990 (Box 77)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Haitian Boat Crisis - December, 1991; 1 of 3 (Box 77)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Haitian Boat Crisis - December, 1991; 2 of 3 (Box 77)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Haitian Boat Crisis - December, 1991; 3 of 3 (Box 77)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Haitian Boat Crisis - July, 1991 (Box 77)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Haitian Boat Crisis - November, 1991; 1 of 2 (Box 77)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Haitian Boat Crisis - November, 1991; 2 of 2 (Box 77)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Haitian Boat Crisis - undated, 1991 (Box 77)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Haitian Boat People, May 1994 (Box 77)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Haitian interdiction campaign, 1989-1990 (Box 78)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Haitian Interdiction Petition, 1995 (Box 78)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - INS and Coast Guard Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 78)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Interdiction articles, 1991 (Box 150)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Interdiction Bill, 1990 (Box 78)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Interdiction documents, 1991; 1 of 4 (Box 78)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Interdiction documents, 1991; 2 of 4 (Box 78)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Interdiction documents, 1991; 3 of 4 (Box 78)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Interdiction documents, 1991; 4 of 4 (Box 78)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Interdiction documents, 1991-1995 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Interdiction Info Packet, 1991 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Interdiction log- US Embassy, 1983 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Interdiction notes, 1989 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Interdiction of Haitians- a disgrace, 1998 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Interdiction press releases, 1989 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Interdiction Statistics, 1984 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Interdictions by US Coast Guards, 1989 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Interviews with repatriated boat people, 1992 (Box 146)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Joint interdiction project with LCHR, 1989 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - letter from NCHR to Mayor Suarez on Interdiction, 1991 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - letter to Bruce Morrison on interdiction, 1989 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - letter to City of Miami Mayor about interdiction, 1991 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - NCHR Coalition to End Haitian Interdiction, 1991 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - NCHR Interdiction Bill, 1990 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - NCHR Interdiction Report, 1988 (Box 79)
  - Boat People/Interdiction - notes on repatriation, 1991 (Box 152)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - PJMC on Haitian interdiction, 1988 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Presentation of Brunson McKinley on US Policy on Haitian Boat People, 1992 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Presidential Documents on Interdiction of Haitian boatpeople, 1989 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - project of Yves Joseph, 1990 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Report on interdiction stats, 1987 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Report on the forced return of boat people, 1993 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Reports from Department of State on Haitian boat people repatriates, 1992; 1 of 2 (Box 79)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Reports from Department of State on Haitian boat people repatriates, 1992; 2 of 2 (Box 80)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Statistics on Haitian Boat People, 1992 (Box 80)
  - Boat People/Interdiction - Suspension of Interdiction, 1991 (Box 152)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - UNMIH MILOB post patrol report, 1994 (Box 151)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - US Coast Guard Investigation of Capsized Haitian sailing vessel, 1985 (Box 80)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - US Coast Guard Telecommunications from Haitian boat people, 1987; 1 of 2 (Box 80)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - US Coast Guard Telecommunications from Haitian boat people, 1987; 2 of 2 (Box 80)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - US Haiti Interdiction agreement, 1981 (Box 80)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - US Supreme Court upholding government right to return refugees on the high seas, 1993 (Box 80)
  - Boat people/Interdiction - Vietnam boat people, 1989 (Box 80)
  - Bouki Club, 1999 (Box 80)
  - Boycott Domsey flyers, 1990 (Box 148)
  - Brief and paperwork filed by Michael Ray, 1990 (Box 80)
  - Brief of participants in Canadian embassy, 1992 (Box 80)
  - Brief on Haiti situation, 1990 (Box 80)
  - Bulletins on Haiti, 1994-1995 (Box 81)
  - Business Council for International Understanding, luncheon with Am. Diego Asenco participant list, 1990 (Box 81)
  - Bylaws of the National Immigration, Refugee, and Citizenship Forum, 1991 (Box 81)
  - CAERD press conference, 1989 (Box 146)
  - Call for assistance from the Caribbean American foundation of California, 1996 (Box 81)
  - Call list for Congress and House of Representatives, undated (Box 81)
  - Campagne Haiti Correspondence/letters, 1994 (Box 81)
  - Campaign for human rights in Haiti, 1990 (Box 81)
  - Campaign for Peace and Democracy, 1991 (Box 81)
  - Campaign of Support, 1994 (Box 81)
  - Campaign to Extend Salvador TPS Bulletin, 1991 (Box 81)
  - Campaign to pressure US action on Haiti, 1992-1993 (Box 81)
  - Canadian Assistance to Haiti, 1991 (Box 81)
  - Canadian organizations on Haitian Service, 1994 (Box 81)
  - Candace Mirando to Mike Hooper, 1987 (Box 149)
  - Capacity building initiative, 2001 (Box 81)
  - Capitol Hill Hearing Testimony, 1994 (Box 149)
  - Cardinal O'Connor's sermon, 1991 (Box 151)
  - Care Statement on Humanitarian Assistance to Haiti Executive Summary, 1993 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean American Foundation of California letters to McCalla, 1994 (Box 150)
  - Caribbean American Foundation of California Mandate, undated (Box 150)
  - Caribbean Association of Media Workers (CAMWORK) protest to a.b. President Joseph Nerette, 1991 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Conference of Churches, 1991 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Conference of Churches/World Council of Churches, 1992 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Human Rights Network- Correspondence with Philippe Lavanchy, 1992 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Human Rights Network faxes, 1992 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean human rights network sixth annual general meeting, 1991 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Human Rights Network to Edwin Carrington, 1994 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Human Rights Press Release, 1992 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Network System to AW/LCHR, 1991 (Box 152)
  - Caribbean NGO's on Haitian crisis - St. Lucia, 1992 (Box 117)
  - Caribbean Rights, 1984 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Rights, 1996 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Rights - Conference in Haiti, 1991 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Rights - general meeting materials, 1989-1992 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Rights - Materials, 1987-1990 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Rights - 8th Annual General meeting, 1993 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Rights - Augustin Romain Ceme, 1989 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Rights - Correspondence/letter to Ricky Singh (Caribbean Rights) Haiti Crisis, 1993 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Rights - Haiti, New Challenges, 1995 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Rights - on Jamaica's Election, 1993 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Rights - Penal Reform International Conference- Conclusions and Recommendations, 1991 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Rights - press release, 1990 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Rights - recommendations to the organization, 1995 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Rights - resolution on Haiti, 1989 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Rights - Sec. of State James Baker III, 1991 (Box 152)
  - Caribbean Rights - Statement on the military coup in Haiti, 1991 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Rights - Third Regional Meeting of Caribbean Rights, 1988 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Rights - updates, 1992-1994 (Box 81)
  - Caribbean Rights, Jamaica's election, 1993 (Box 146)
  - Caribbean Unity Fund, 2002 (Box 82)
  - Caribbean Women's Health Association Community Service Centers, 1997 (Box 82)
  - Caribbean Women's' Health Center, 2000 (Box 82)
  - Caribbean/Haitian Program Statement of Needs, 1986 (Box 82)
  - Caribbean-Haitian Program, 1988 (Box 149)
  - CARICOM on Haiti, 1990 (Box 82)
  - CARICOM statement, 1991 (Box 82)
  - Carl Henri Rechardson and Jean Rabel committee, 1992 (Box 82)
  - Carmean arrests, 1989 (Box 82)
  - Carnegie Endowment from International Peace, 1993 (Box 82)
  - Carnegie Roundtable on Haitian Migration Policy, 1991 (Box 82)
  - Casa de Proyecto Libertad Press Release, 1990 (Box 82)
  - Case of Border Patrol Agent- Michael Elmer, 1993 (Box 82)
  - CATH "In the Name of the Haitian People", 1987 (Box 82)
  - CATH Correspondence/letter, 1990 (Box 82)
  - CATH declaration, 1989 (Box 82)
  - CATH Declaration, 1989 (Box 82)
  - CATH press Correspondence/letter, 1990 (Box 82)
  - CATH press release, 1988-1989 (Box 82)
  - CATH statement, 1989 (Box 82)
  - CCR-Materials, 1994 (Box 82)
  - CDS-Centers for Development and Health, 1992 (Box 82)
  - Celebration of International Creole Day, 1992 (Box 82)
  - Cen. Lafontant Joseph, 1991 (Box 82)
  - Center for Constitutional Rights statement, 1991 (Box 82)
  - Center for Global Education- Haiti Study Trip, 1988 (Box 82)
  - Center for Human Rights and Constitution Law memo, 1993 (Box 82)
  - Center for Human Rights and Constitutional Law, 1993 (Box 82)
  - Center for Human Rights and Constitutional Law, Vellejou- INS settlement developments, 1991 (Box 82)
  - Center for Human Rights Promotion Correspondence/letters, 1988 (Box 82)
  - Center for Immigrant Rights correspondence, 1990 (Box 149)
  - Center for Immigrants Rights Conference invitation, 1987 (Box 148)
  - Center for Immigrants Rights folder, 1988-1989 (Box 82)
  - Center for Immigrants Rights program summary, 1985 (Box 82)
  - Center for International Policy, 1994 (Box 82)
  - Center for St. Emaus reports, 1997 (Box 82)
  - Center Lafontant Joseph protests, 1989 (Box 83)
  - Centre de Promotion des Droits Humains, 1987 (Box 148)
  - Centre Karl Leveque, 1987 (Box 83)
  - CEP, 1990 (Box 83)
  - CEP (electronic council), 1990 (Box 132)
  - CEP folders, 1989 (Box 83)
  - CEP press release, 1990 (Box 83)
  - CHADEL - (Haitian Center for Human Rights) press release on military repression, 1989 (Box 83)